class Global {
  List<Map<String, dynamic>> allquestion = [
    {
      "question": "1.the international litercy day is observed on",
      "correct_answer": "sep 8",
      "answers": [
        "sep 8",
        "nov 28",
        "may 2",
        "sep 22",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The theme of the World Red Cross and Red Crescent Day was?",
      "correct_answer": " Dignity for all – focus on Children",
      "answers": [
        "Nourishment for all-focus on children",
        "Focus on health for all",
        "Dignity for all – focus on Children",
        "Dignity for all – focus on women",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "3. which of the following corresponds to 'ek bataa'do",
      "correct_answer": "Adha",
      "answers": [
        "pura",
        "sawa",
        "Adha",
        "pauna",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question":
          "4. In the game of ludo the discs or tokens are of how many colors",
      "correct_answer": "four",
      "answers": [
        "one",
        "two",
        "three",
        "four",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question":
          "5. Released in 2001, the first edition of Apple&#039;s Mac OS Xoperating system (version 10.0) was given what animal code name?",
      "correct_answer": "Cheetah",
      "answers": [
        "Puma",
        "Cheetah",
        "Tiger",
        "Leopard",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "6.where was the Brics summit held in 2014?",
      "correct_answer": "brazil",
      "answers": [
        "brazil",
        "india",
        "russia",
        "china",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "7. Which of these terms can only be used for women?",
      "correct_answer": " Suhagan",
      "answers": [
        "Dirghaayu",
        " Suhagan",
        "Chiranjeevi",
        "Sushil",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question":
          "8. Which of these is not a layer in the OSI model for data communications?",
      "correct_answer": "Connection Layer",
      "answers": [
        "Application Layer",
        "Transport Layer",
        "Connection Layer",
        "Physical Layer",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question":
          "9.Who wrote the introduction to the English translation of Rabindranath Tagore’s Gitanjali?",
      "correct_answer": " W.B. Yeats ",
      "answers": [
        " P.B. Shelley ",
        "Alfred Tennyson",
        " W.B. Yeats",
        "T.S. Elliot",
      ]
    },
    {
      "question":
          "10.Which of these are names of national parks located in MadhyaPradesh?",
      "correct_answer": "Kanha and Madhav",
      "answers": [
        "Kanha and Madhav",
        "Krishna and Kanhaiya",
        "Ghanshyam and Murari",
        "Girdhar and Gopal",
      ]
    }
  ];
}
